<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web on Jonot&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://jonot.me/tags/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web on Jonot&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:13:16 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jonot.me/tags/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sitelen Pona Tester</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/sitelen-pona-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:13:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/sitelen-pona-tester/</guid>
      <description>toki! mi pali e lipu sin
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve released my new website that allows you to practice sitelen pona symbols, by giving you a symbol and four words, and you have to select the one that matches:
Alright, maybe I should explain somethings
Toki Pona Toki Pona is a conlang created by Sonja Lang in 2001. A conlang is a language that was created deliberately, instead of emerging naturally.
One of the main principles of Toki Pona is minimalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of GIF Replacements</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/video-format-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/video-format-comparison/</guid>
      <description>IMPORTANT NOTE I have repeatedly had problems with this article due to the large file size of the videos. At this point I have decided to reduce all of the videos to 1 second to reduce this. The text all applies still, but you&amp;rsquo;ll have to encode the files yourself if you want to see what they look like in full.
The GIF file format was created in 1987, and it definitely shows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reader Mode</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/reader-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/reader-mode/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever been on a website? It can be really annoying. Many pages have an absurd amount of ads, and a lot of sites have limits on how much you can read before they ask you to sign up for some account or get a newsletter or whatever.
It&amp;rsquo;s annoying enough, but it&amp;rsquo;s more annoying on a dual-core Intel Celeron processor with 4 GB of ram. So a while ago, I created a bookmarklet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
