<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on Jonot&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://jonot.me/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on Jonot&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 14:47:45 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jonot.me/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Silverblue</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/fedora-silverblue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 14:47:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/fedora-silverblue/</guid>
      <description>Since the beginning of January I have been using Fedora Silverblue on my home computer. In this article, I thought that I would explain a bit about how I use it, why, and the pros and cons of using it for general use and development
What is Fedora Silverblue? As this website states, Fedora Silverblue is a variant of Fedora Workstation where the root filesystem is immutable, meaning you can&amp;rsquo;t change it, which makes every root installation the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The longest word you can spell in hexadecimal</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/hex-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:08:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/hex-words/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;coldblooded&amp;rdquo;
This is something that I did a while ago, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d just write a post about it. Here is a shell script to get every word that can be spelled with hexadecimal, sorted by length:
cat /usr/share/dict/words | tr &amp;#34;[:upper:]&amp;#34; &amp;#34;[:lower:]&amp;#34; | grep -E &amp;#34;^[abcdeflzso]+$&amp;#34; | tr &amp;#34;lzso&amp;#34; &amp;#34;1250&amp;#34; | awk &amp;#39;{print length, &amp;#34;0x&amp;#34; $0}&amp;#39; | sort -nr -k 1 | cut -d &amp;#34; &amp;#34; -f 2 If that seems incredibly cryptic to you, don&amp;rsquo;t worry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Android</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/running-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 19:02:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/running-android/</guid>
      <description>WARNING: This blog post comes with no warranty. It should be made clear that I do not know any of what I am doing.
I recently found out that Waydroid, a container-based system to run android apps on Linux, got added to the Fedora repos. I have occasionally tried installing Waydroid with very little success, but this official support from my distro gave me new hope. So I decided to try it out again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
