<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Jonot&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://jonot.me/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Jonot&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:13:16 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jonot.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sitelen Pona Tester</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/sitelen-pona-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 16:13:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/sitelen-pona-tester/</guid>
      <description>toki! mi pali e lipu sin
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve released my new website that allows you to practice sitelen pona symbols, by giving you a symbol and four words, and you have to select the one that matches:
Alright, maybe I should explain somethings
Toki Pona Toki Pona is a conlang created by Sonja Lang in 2001. A conlang is a language that was created deliberately, instead of emerging naturally. The most famous example of this is Esperanto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of GIF Replacements</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/video-format-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/video-format-comparison/</guid>
      <description>The GIF file format was created in 1987, and it definitely shows. Despite being so widespread on the internet, it has several issues. First of all is color. Most images that you will see on the internet use 24-bit color. Each pixel has a red, green, and blue component, all of which can range from 0-255. This gives you a total of 16,777,216 possible colors. So how many does GIF have?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reader Mode</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/reader-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/reader-mode/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever been on a website? It can be really annoying. Many pages have an absurd amount of ads, and a lot of sites have limits on how much you can read before they ask you to sign up for some account or get a newsletter or whatever.
It&amp;rsquo;s annoying enough, but it&amp;rsquo;s more annoying on a dual-core Intel Celeron processor with 4 GB of ram. So a while ago, I created a bookmarklet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas</title>
      <link>https://jonot.me/posts/ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 17:30:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jonot.me/posts/ideas/</guid>
      <description>Ideas is a really simple program, and yet out of all of the programs I have made, it is probably the one I have used the most. It&amp;rsquo;s so short, in fact, that I&amp;rsquo;ll just put the entire source code into this post:
#!/usr/bin/env python3 from pathlib import Path import os # Folder for ideas IDEAS_FOLDER = Path(os.environ[&amp;#34;HOME&amp;#34;]) / &amp;#34;.local/share/ideas/&amp;#34; def main(): title = input(&amp;#34;What is your idea? &amp;#34;) print(&amp;#34;Interesting, tell me more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
